https://www.aimmedia.com/privacy-policy/?__hstc=176285754.6be47955373008db196536135a454fd3.1564683880987.1578585875106.1578592004394.69&__hssc=176285754.11.1578592004394&__hsfp=3869936477

Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or magazine, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, location, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, use our sites without registering, although some content and/or sections may become inaccessible. When using AIM mobile applications registration and/or login may be required to access the materials.
Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
; To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
; To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
; To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
; To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.
; To send periodic messages via email and postal mail
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc. We may also send promotional messages to an email or postal mail address that our cookies associate with you when you browse our sites.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
Notwithstanding any other provision, we may engage a data provider who may collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system) via a tracking pixel, or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content through web, mobile or other media channels. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these data provider cookies, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices or http://www.networkadvertising/choices.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
These security measures may include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology via HTTPS urls to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers’ systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies for our own purposes on the sites and our partners may also use cookies on our sites to fulfill purposes that we specify that we believe are consistent with this privacy policy.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, rent, loan, or give your email address or other personal information to anybody without your express permission. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may provide third-party vendors with encrypted (i.e. hashed) data that is not identifiable via personal information such as email, phone, address, etc. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
From time to time, our sponsors wish to contact our subscribers and customers who have indicated an interest in their products, services or events. Before we disclose your personally identifiable data to a third party for their own business purposes (such as a survey or a sweepstake), we will first obtain your consent, for example via email, click-through, an online opportunity to opt-out or otherwise. If you register for or access products, services or events offered by these vendors, you choose to share your name and contact details directly with those vendors so that they may contact you. For example, if you register for a vendor-branded (or co-branded with us) resource, we will collect your registration information on behalf of that vendor for its own use. When you register for an in-person or online event, we will provide your registration information to the sponsor(s) of such event. If you want to know how a vendor or advertiser will use data about you, we urge you to check that vendor’s or advertiser’s privacy policy.
Also see, “Third party partnerships/platform operations” and “Third party links” details below.
How Can You Opt Out of Use and Disclosure of Your Information?
Active Interest Media will only use your personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or as subsequently authorized by you. You can avoid having your personal information disclosed to sponsors in the following ways: a) do not provide us with personal information; b) do not access or request content; c) turn on cookie and/or ad blocking via your browser; or d) email us at privacy@aimmedia.com to request that we opt-out your email address from Active Interest Media emails. Active Interest Media has a number of brands and products and we allow you to opt-out selectively. If you wish to remove your email address only from a specific brand, please use the opt-out mechanism provided in emails you receive from such brand, make use of a provided “private account” option to prevent search and follow capabilities, or contact the brand directly.
To opt-out of postal mail promotions from Active Interest Media, please mail an opt-out request to us at:
Active Interest Media | Attn: Circulation Department
5710 Flatiron Parkway
Suite A
Boulder CO 80301
You can direct your opt-out request to specific brands or to ‘all brands.’
You may receive email marketing messages from us about our own or other companies’ offerings. To opt-out of a partner marketing email program, you may follow the instructions at the bottom of any email we send you as part of the program.
You may withdraw your consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. To withdraw your consent, simply contact us by writing to the Active Interest Media, Inc., 5720 Flatiron Pkwy, Boulder, CO 80301, USA Attn: Data Department, or by e-mailing us at privacy@aimmedia.com and advising which of your personal information you no longer wish us to collect, use and/or disclose. We will the inform you of the implications of withdrawing consent to collect, use and/or disclose that personal information, including without limitation the fact that once such consent is withdrawn you may not be able to use certain or all of the features of the Site, applications or services, and/or may not be able to receive products and services from us. Should you nonetheless still desire that consent be withdrawn, we will accede to your request.
We may work with data providers to target advertising to you personally, through online and offline methods including email, display media and direct mail. This advertising may be directed to you because you visited or logged in to our website. When we generate this advertising, data we collect from you through online cookies, tracking pixels, and other technologies may be combined with other de-identified data (such as a hashed, non-readable email or postal address) in order to tailor ads to you based on your preferences and other information about you. To learn more about targeted advertising, these providers, or how you may opt out, please visit the DAA’s consumer choice page at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Or read Google’s Privacy and Terms here: https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites You can also learn more from our advertising and technology partner Say Media: https://www.saymedia.com/privacy.
Premium Accounts
Information may be collected in order to process your payments (e.g., for subscriptions);
We may offer the ability to sign up for a premium account that allows you to visit the Site without, or with limited, advertisements (a “Premium Account”). If you use a Premium Account, we will not use personal information about you for advertising purposes.
If you choose to use an account, you are responsible for keeping your login credentials for access to certain parts of the site (e.g., user names and passwords) confidential. Do not give your credentials to anyone else.
Notice that we may share personal information with service providers, subcontractors, partners, vendors, consultants, and others that help us with any of the purposes noted above or otherwise in this Policy
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our websites. We may collect a share of sales or other compensation from third-party links (via e-commerce affiliate linking) on our websites or digital entities. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Third party partnerships/platform operations
Active Interest Media utilizes a platform owned by Maven Coalition, Inc. (“Maven”) to host and manage its content and to show ads on a number of our websites.* Maven may receive the personal information you provide through Active Interest Media websites, including information you provide when you request information, or provide login or profile information.  Maven may use such personal information for its own purposes, such as to enable you to login on other sites that use Maven’s technology, to show you ads, or to communicate with you. To learn more about how Maven handles personal information, visit Maven’s Privacy Policy.
Active Interest Media, Maven, and other third parties may provide, or allow others to provide, analytics services and serve advertisements on our or their behalf across the web and in mobile applications. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers and other technologies to collect information about your visits to our websites and other websites and mobile applications. This information may include your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked, and conversion information. This information may be used by Active Interest Media, Maven, and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our website and other websites, and better understand your online activity.
To see all available opt out options for users of sites that operate on the Maven platform, please visit Maven’s Privacy Policy.
*Active Interest Media websites using Maven’s platform are clearly identified as a Maven channel in the website’s footer.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
CAN-SPAM Compliance
We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.
This policy was last modified on November 5, 2020.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Active Interest Media | Attn: Circulation Department
5720 Flatiron Pkwy
Boulder, CO 80301
privacy@aimmedia.com
Privacy Policy Customer Pledge
We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:
Federal Trade Commision Fair
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act
Privacy Alliance
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
Trust Guard Privacy Requirements
